

PAUL AWOLESI

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Multi-faceted software developer who is knowledgeable in HTML, JavaScript and Python. A true team player offering 3 years of experience in the software industry. Seeking the opportunity to provide outstanding, clean code in a collaborative environment.

awolesiboluwatife@gmail.com

Malta

in linkedin.com/in/paul-awolesi

+2348091478957

www.cypherspot.xyz

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Devloper Fessburn

05/2020 - Present

Re-organized something to make it work better.

Responsible for creative design for prominent interface.
Consistently managed client needs through research resulting in positive results. Researched and updated all required materials needed for firm and partners. Worked closely with CEO to establish and deliver to customer needs.

Python Developer Coinvasity

09/2019 - 05/2020

Improved on my collaboration skill

 Improved marketing system by adding new features and infrastructure, enhancing productivity. Worked closely with UI/UX Designer to maintain optimum levels of communication for the effective and efficient completion of project.

Junior Python Developer Delideas Solution

12/2018 - 07/2019

Build complex python application

To design and develop solutions to complex programmatic problems

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology University of Ibadan

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Telegram bot

I made use of the "telepot" module to connect to the telegram api. The bot registers and saves the: email address of the user, twitter username, telegram username, facebook url, user etherum address into a database. It allows for editing of previous entries. It creates a referal system. Export the data into a csv file.

School Website and Blog Interface

 It has the usual school website pages like the Home, Executives, About, Gallery, Event, a Blog and an Alumni page. The blog interface has and admin page where you can publish your articles, It has a comment and tagging system, The Alumni webpage also has a blogging system and a forum webpage.

Django and React Application

 It is a Todo Application that show the complete and incomplete task. It allows for editing and deleting of task that has already been completed. The React Application uses the "axios" library to connect to the backend Django Application.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Received awards (05/2020 - 06/2020)

Identified a problem and solved it (07/2019 - Present)

Worked on special projects (04/2020 - 08/2020)

LANGUAGES

French English

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Technology | Software Development

Data Science

Python